Guide to the Jazz Loft Project Records, 1950-2012 and undated RL.10001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Materials
  - Electronic Files, 2004-2009 and undated; 1
    - Scans for Book, 2008 November; 7
      - Compact disc, 2008 November (Box 32, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0128)
    - 6th Avenue Map from New York Public Library, 2008 October; 8
      - Compact disc, 2008 October (Box 32, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0127)
    - Jazz Loft Book Scans, 2008 September; 9
      - Compact disc, 2008 September (Box 31, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0087)
    - Jazz Loft web images, 2008 September; 10
      - Compact disc, 2008 September (Box 31, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0082)
    - Jazz Loft Town Hall site images and logos, 2008 September 26; 11
      - Compact disc, 2008 September 26 (Box 31, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0080)
    - Jazz Loft Town Hall site images and logos, 2008 September 26; 12
      - Compact disc, 2008 September 26 (Box 31, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0081)
    - Dec. 2009 Archive Backup, 13
      - Compact disc, 2009 (Box 31, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0073)
    - Jazz Loft Splinter Group, 2009 July 1; 15
      - Compact disc, 2009 July 1 (Box 34, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0178)
    - "Deceased" postage stamp, undated; 16
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 34, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0195)
    - Dan Partridge research files, undated; 17
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 32, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0119)
    - David X. Young Digital Catalog, undated; 18
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 32, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0133)
    - Exhibition Mailings, undated; 19
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 34, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0175)
    - Final "Master" Access Jazz Loft Project Database, undated; 20
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 31, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0063)
    - Following Monk booklet, undated; 21
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 31, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0090)
    - Jazz Loft Files, undated; 22
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 34, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0209)
    - Jazz Loft Project Book Scans, undated; 23
      - DVD, undated (Box 33, Optical-disc RL10001-DVD-0010)
    - Jazz Loft TV/Radio Exhibit, undated; 24
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 33, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0170)
    - Jazz Loft web images, undated; 25
      - compact disc, undated (Box 31, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0086)
    - Karales Powerpoint presentation, undated; 26
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 35, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0218)
    - Lauren Brenner research report, undated; 27
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 32, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0118)
    - Logo scans, undated; 28
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 34, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0211)
    - Monk Poster for Print, undated; 29
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 34, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0193)
    - Playlist 3 Website Draft, undated; 30
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 34, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0181)
    - Playlist 3 Website Draft, undated; 31
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 34, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0182)
    - Playlist for Chaos Manor, undated; 32
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 34, Optical-disc RL10001-CD-0187)
- Associated Audiovisual Materials, 1967-2010 and undated; 1; 210 items
  This series contains audiovisual materials collected during the research and oral history interview phases of the Jazz Loft Project, as well as excerpts, playlists, and compilations of audio and video put together for radio programs, podcasts, and the Jazz Loft website. Materials are generally related to individuals associated with the Jazz Loft, with jazz music in general, and with the New York art scene of the mid-20th century. Of particular note are original audio recordings made of Hall Overton's opera "Huckleberry Finn", which was performed at the Juilliard School in 1971, as well as other recordings of Overton given to the Jazz Loft Project by Hall Overton's widow, Nancy Overton. Other materials include copies of the recordings, made for transcription, that W. Eugene Smith made at the Jazz Loft; recordings of Jason Moran and the 2007-2009 interpretations of Thelonious Monk's Town Hall Concert; and commercial audio and video recordings. Original recordings are closed to use, although copies of recordings may be made available to researchers. Contact the Rubenstein Library for further information.
  - Hall Overton
    - Woodwind Octet - Hall Overton. Recordings of Friday night broadcast over WNYC, from Juilliard School of Music, conductor Irving Hoffman. Instrumentation: 1 flute; 1 oboe; 2 B flat clarinets; 1 bass clarinet; 2 horns in F; 1 bassoon., 1949
      - Original 12-inch lacquer phonodisc (Box 38, Audio-phonodisc RL10001-PD-0002)
    - THREE FOR DUKE - Teddy Charles, Oscar Pettiford, Hall Overton. Jubilee Records, acetate reference recording. Side 1: "Sherman Shuffle"; "Main Stem"; "Do Nothing Until You Hear From Me." Side 2: "Don't Get Around Much Anymore"; "The Mooch"; "Sophisticated Lady.", 1957
      - Original 12-inch lacquer phonodisc (Box 38, Audio-phonodisc RL10001-PD-0001)
      - Compact disc, copy 1 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0140)
      - Compact disc, copy 2 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0142)
    - Excerpts from IN THREE ATTITUDES - Jimmy Raney, Red Mitchell, Osie Johnson, Hall Overton. Ampar Records acetate reference recording. Songs: "On the Rocks"; "Strike Up the Band"; "Indian Summer.", 1957
      - Original 10-inch lacquer phonodisc (Box 38, Audio-phonodisc RL10001-PD-0003)
    - Sonorities for Orchestra (Orchestra U.S.A.), 1965
      - Compact disc, copy 1 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0140)
      - Compact disc, copy 2 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0142)
    - Hall Overton Concert & Lecture at Williamsport, PA, 1967
      - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 37, Audio-reel RL10001-RR-0005)
      - Compact disc, part 1 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0156)
      - Compact disc, part 2 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0157)
      - Compact disc, part 3 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0158)
    - HUCKLEBERRY FINN - Hall Overton, circa 1971
      - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape, act 1 (Box 37, Audio-reel RL10001-RR-0001)
      - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape, act 2, part 1 (Box 37, Audio-reel RL10001-RR-0002)
      - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape, act 2, part 2 (Box 37, Audio-reel RL10001-RR-0003)
      - Compact disc, act 1, copy 1 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0151)
      - Compact disc, act 1, copy 2 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0152)
      - Compact disc, act 1, copy 3 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0147)
      - Compact disc, act 2, part 1 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0154)
      - Compact disc, act 2, part 2 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0155)
      - Compact disc, act 2 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0148)
      - Compact disc, copy 1 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0149)
      - Compact disc, copy 2 (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0150)
    - Hall Overton and Cal & David X. Young Discussing Art, undated
      - Compact disc (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0146)
    - Hall Overton Interview, undated
      - Compact disc (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0145)
    - Hall Overton Interview with Billy Taylor, undated
      - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 37, Audio-reel RL10001-RR-0004)
    - Hall Overton Tapes--Bill Dixon Radio Interview with Hall Overton, undated
      - Compact disc (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0160)
    - Hall Overton Tapes--Concertino for Viola and Strings Rehearsal, undated
      - Compact disc (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0162)
    - Hall Overton Tapes--Hall, Teddy Charles, Ed Shaugnessy Rehearsal and Jam Session, undated
      - Compact disc (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0161)
    - Hall Overton Tapes--NET Show "Jazz is Music", undated
      - Compact disc (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0159)
    - Hall Overton--Bangor, MI, 2006 August 18
      - Compact disc (Box 34, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0205)
    - Sonata V&P; Sonata V&C; 2nd String Quartet; Symphony #2 in one movement - Hall Overton.
      - Compact disc, undated (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0141)
    - "Can't Get Started"; "Original by Hall" - Hall Overton., undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 38, Audio-phonodisc RL10001-PD-0004)
  - W. Eugene Smith
    - W. Eugene Smith, jazz recordings, undated; 141
      - Center for Creative Photography W. Eugene Smith Jazz Recordings Feb. 26, 1959, undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0238)
      - Center for Creative Photography W. Eugene Smith Jazz Recordings; Tape: "Probable Cause" Winter 59-60 1/4 track one side only; Treistman Center Audio Restoration, undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0237)
      - Center for Creative Photography W. Eugene Smith Jazz Recordings; Tape 6/6/60 OA 1/4 track mono sides 1 & 3; Treistman Center Audio Restoration, undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0235)
      - Center for Creative Photography W. Eugene Smith Jazz Recordings; Tape 6/6/60 OA 1/4 track mono side 2; Treistman Center Audio Restoration, undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0236)
    - W. Eugene Smith, sample tracks from Smith's audiotapes, undated; 142
      - Jazz Loft: W. Eugene Smith in New York City, 1957-65; Sample tracks from Smith's audiotapes, W. Eugene Smith Archive at the Center for Creative Photography, undated, Compact disc (Box 31, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0064)
      - Jazz Loft: W. Eugene Smith in New York City, 1957-65; Sample tracks from Smith's audiotapes, W. Eugene Smith Archive at the Center for Creative Photography, undated, Compact disc (Box 31, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0065)
      - Jazz Loft: W. Eugene Smith in New York City, 1957-65; Sample tracks from Smith's audiotapes, W. Eugene Smith Archive at the Center for Creative Photography, undated, Compact disc (Box 31, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0066)
      - Jazz Loft: W. Eugene Smith in New York City, 1957-65; Sample tracks from Smith's audiotapes, W. Eugene Smith Archive at the Center for Creative Photography, undated, Compact disc (Box 31, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0067)
      - Jazz Loft: W. Eugene Smith in New York City, 1957-65; Sample tracks from Smith's audiotapes, W. Eugene Smith Archive at the Center for Creative Photography, undated, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0099)
      - Jazz Loft: W. Eugene Smith in New York City, 1957-65; Sample tracks from Smith's audiotapes, W. Eugene Smith Archive at the Center for Creative Photography, undated, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0100)
    - W. Eugene Smith, audio reels, undated; 143
      - Smith Audio Reels, 1-4, undated, Standard audio-cassette (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0102)
      - Smith Audio Reels, 5-6, undated, Standard audio-cassette (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0103)
      - Audio-Smith, Reel #7-8, undated, Standard audio-cassette (Box 27, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0104)
      - Smith Audio 9-10, undated, Standard audio-cassette (Box 28, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0105)
      - Smith Audio 11-12, undated, Standard audio-cassette (Box 28, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0106)
      - Smith Audio 12 cont'd, undated, Standard audio-cassette (Box 28, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0107)
      - Side A: W. Eugene Smith: Reel 13, Tape 2, Track 5 - "Paradise Garden Monologue", (919) 724-3665, poperty CDS/CCP, Side B: Reel 199, CD 5, Tracks 1,2, Gene Smith "Cheryl", David Young, ~11 min. excerpt, Reel 147, CD #1 &2, Track: 6, Smith Monologue, undated, Standard audio-cassette (Box 28, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0108)
      - W. Eugene Smith: Garden 199, 5/5, 1, excerpt, undated, Standard audio-cassette (Box 28, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0109)
      - W. Eugene Smith: Lamp unto my feet, CBS, 1971, undated, Standard audio-cassette (Box 28, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0110)
    - Eugene Smith BBC Bristol, undated; 28
      - Eugene Smith BBC Bristol 2005, undated, Compact disc (Box 34, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0207)
    - W. Eugene Smith, 1971 audio, undated; 140
      - Smith 1971 Audio 11 (12), undated, Compact disc (Box 34, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0189)
      - Smith 1971 Audio 9-10 (10-11), undated, Compact disc (Box 34, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0190)
      - Smith 1971 Audio 8-9, undated, Compact disc (Box 34, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0191)
      - Smith 1971 Audio 5-7, undated, Compact disc (Box 34, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0192)
      - Smith 1971 Audio 1-4, undated, Compact disc (Box 31, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0079)
  - 821 6th Ave, 2002 November 12; 1
    - 821 6th Ave, 11/12/2002, Director: Sam Stephenson, Camera: Paul Gentry, MASTER, 2002 November 12, Mini-dv videocassette (Box 24, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0131)
  - A Tribute to the Greats, undated; 2
    - A Tribute to the Greats; Sal Salvador gtr featuring Eddie Costa; Frank Balboa-bass, R. Free-Drums; Rex. 6/3, 4, 5 1967, undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0217)
    - A Tribute to the Greats; Sal Salvador gtr featuring Eddie Costa; Frank Balboa-bass, R. Free-Drums; Rex. 6/3, 4, 5 1967, undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0219)
  - Adirondack Ballads and Folk Songs, undated; 3
    - Adirondack Ballads and Folk Songs; From lumberwoods, iron mines, and communities; Sung by Lee Knight, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0283)
  - Ambient Comp JL Project, undated; 4
    - Ambient Comp JL Project, undated, Compact disc (Box 31, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0074)
  - An American Garden, undated; 5
    - Dave Tofani; An American Garden, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0300)
  - Audio for Jazz at Lincoln Center Presentation, 2008 November; 6
    - audio Jazz@Lincoln Center presentation 11.08, 2008 November, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0126)
  - Best of the Majic Spirit Band 70's, 80's, 90's, undated; 7
    - Best of the Majic Spirit Band 70's, 80's, 90's; Earle Davis and the Majic Spirit Band, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0273)
  - Beyond Words: Photographers of War, 2005; 8
    - Beyond Words: Photographers of War, 2005, DVD (Box 33, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0009)
  - Bird Calls Vol I with the Hall Overton Quartet, undated; 9
    - Bird Calls, Vol I; Dail Woods w/the Hall Overton Quartet & Wellington Quartet, undated, Compact disc (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0163)
  - BMQ, undated; 10
    - BMQ, undated, Compact disc (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0166)
  - Brilliant Fever: W. Eugene Smith & Pittsburgh, 2001; 11
    - Brilliant Fever: W. Eugene Smith & Pittsburgh, 2001, VHS (Box 37, Video-cassette RL10001-VHS-0003)
    - Brilliant Fever: W. Eugene Smith & Pittsburgh; 30 mins, undated, VHS (Box 37, Video-cassette RL10001-VHS-0004)
    - W. Eugene Smith Brilliant Fever + Extras, undated, DVD (Box 34, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0014)
  - Brotherly Jazz-The Heath Brothers, 2006; 12
    - Brotherly Jazz-The Heath Brothers, 2006, DVD (Box 37, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0017)
  - Carol Lian Piano Plays Scarlatti, Ravel, Reilly, Briggs, Gershwin, undated; 13
    - Carol Lian Piano Plays Scarlatti, Ravel, Reilly, Briggs, Gershwin, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0285)
  - Cecil Taylor, 2007; 14
    - Artists House Presents: The Jazz Master Class Series From NYU; Cecil Taylor, 2007, DVD (Box 37, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0018)
  - Celebration! Music of 4 Continents in an Afro-Jazz Setting, undated; 15
    - Celebration! Music of 4 Continents in an Afro-Jazz Setting; Brother Ah's World Music Ensemble, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0266)
  - Chasin' the Blues, undated; 16
    - Chasin' the Blues; The Jim Cullum Jazz Band; Riverwalk Jazz, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0271)
  - Clarinet alla Cinema, undated; 17
    - Clarinet all Cinema; Nino Rota: Trio; Richard Rodney Bennett: Quintet; Dick Hyman: Sextet; Charles Russo, clarinet, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0272)
  - Concertino for VLA & Strings Rehearsal, undated; 18
    - Concertino for VLA & Strings Rehearsal--Hall Overton, undated, 1/4-inch (Box 37, Audio-reel RL10001-RR-0006)
  - David X. Young tape excerpts, undated; 19
    - David X Young tape excerpts, undated, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0109)
  - David X. Young Tribute, 2002 June 26; 20
    - Ira Jackson and David X. Young Tribute, 6/26/02, 2002 June 26, Mini-dv videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0056)
    - David X. Young Tribute III, Jazz Gallery, 6/26/02, 2002 June 26, Mini-dv videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0057)
  - David X. Young's Jazz Loft, 2000; 21
    - David X. Young's Jazz Loft: 1954-1965 The History and Lost Recordings, 2000, Compact disc (Box 37, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0311)
    - David X. Young's Jazz Loft: 1954-1965 The History and Lost Recordings, 2000, Compact disc (Box 37, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0312)
  - Dick Cary's Tuesday Night Friends--Catching Up, undated; 22
    - Dick Cary's Tuesday Night Friends; Catching Up; the renowned all-star jazz band directed by Dick Hamilton, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0270)
  - Don't Look Back, undated; 23
    - Warren Vache and the Scottish Ensemble; Don't Look Back, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0304)
  - Dream Street Master Soundtrack, undated; 24
    - Dream Street Soundtrack Master, undated, Compact disc (Box 30, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0252)
  - Duke Jazz Talks: Hall Overton: Out of the Shadows, 2010; 25
    - New York Library for the Performing Arts Duke Jazz Talks: Hall Overton: Out of the Shadows, 2010, DVD (Box 32, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0006)
  - Ellis Marsalis Ruminations in New York, undated; 26
    - Ellis Marsalis Ruminations in New York, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0287)
  - Emerson String Quartet, Late Bach String Quartets, undated; 27
    - unlabeled, undated, Compact disc (Box 31, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0095)
  - Exhibit 1 Jazz, undated; 29
    - 1st version, track 3 cue 1:47-4:48, undated, Compact disc (Box 31, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0068)
  - Experiment in Truth, undated; 30
    - Rene Marie; Experiment in Truth, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0286)
  - Flying Saucers-Serious Business by Frank Edwards, undated; 31
    - Frank Edwards 11/1/1959; Long John Nebel WOR NY; By Frank Edwards Flying Saucers-Serious Business Overwhelming New Evidence That They Are Real!!!!!!!!!!!, undated, Compact disc (Box 33, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0136)
  - for monk: a tribute to the music of thelonious monk, undated; 32
    - for monk: a tribute to the music of thelonious monk; BMG Jazz Foundations, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0276)
  - Free Spirit, undated; 33
    - Free Spirit; Ron Free Reads the Words of Martin Cecil, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0279)
  - Frog and Nightgown clips, undated; 34
    - Frog & Nightgown Clips Tks. 1. 2. 3., undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0212)
    - Frog & Nightgown Clips Tks. 1. 2. 3., undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0251)
  - From the Appalachians, undated; 35
    - Lee Knight; From the Appalachians, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0284)
  - Henry Butler at Duke's Following Monk, 2007 October 4; 52
    - Henry Butler 1/2 10-4-07, 2007 October 4, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0225)
    - Henry Butler @ Duke Following Monk 10/4/07; Disc 1 of 2, undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0221)
    - Henry Butler 2/2 10/4/07, undated, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0222)
    - Henry Butler at Duke Following Mon 10/4/07; I, 2007 October 4, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0223)
    - Henry Butler at Duke Following Mon 10/4/07; II, 2007 October 14, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0224)
    - Henry Butler at Duke Following Mon 10/4/07; Disc 2 of 2, 2007 October 4, Compact disc (Box 30, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0262)
  - Hod Meets Barry, undated; 53
    - Hod Meets Barry; Hod O'Brien Trio with Barry Harris, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0289)
  - How to Draw a Bunny (Ray Johnson documentary), undated; 54
    - How to Draw a Bunny, undated, VHS (Box 37, Video-cassette RL10001-VHS-0002)
  - Improvised [Jeremy Steig + Vic Juris], undated; 55
    - Improvised [Jeremy Steig + Vic Juris], undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0299)
  - In My Mind opener, undated; 56
    - In My Min opening 3 min, undated, DVD (Box 32, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0007)
  - Innocence-Green Spring Suite, undated; 57
    - Jack Reilly Trio; Innocence-Green Spring Suite, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0292)
  - Interfaith Meditations, undated; 58
    - Interfaith Meditations; Carman Moore, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0288)
  - Jack Reilly Tributes, undated; 59
    - Jack Reilly Tributes, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0296)
  - Jack Reilly Trio--Blue-Sean-Green, undated; 60
    - Jack Reilly Trio--Blue-Sean-Green, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0291)
  - Jack Reilly: A Jazz Requiem Mass, undated; 61
    - Jack Reilly: A Jazz Requiem Mass, undated, VHS (Box 37, Video-cassette RL10001-VHS-0001)
  - Jack Reilly-Live in Poland, undated; 62
    - Jack Reilly; Live in Poland, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0293)
  - Jam, undated; 63
    - Jam; Eddie Gomez, Jeremy Steig; Vol. 1, undated, Compact disc (Box 36, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0281)
  - Jass is a Lady, undated; 64
    - Jass is a Lady (dupe), undated, audio-cassette (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0143)
  - Jazz Loft Archive Compilation of Non-Music Excerpts, undated; 65
    - Jazz Loft Archive Compilation of Non-Music Excerpts, undated, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0101)
  - Jazz Loft Dialogue Sampler, undated; 66
    - Loft Sampler Dialogue Smith Monologue, undated, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0103)
  - Jazz Loft Excerpts, 2004 September 24; 67
    - Loft Excepts 9/24/04, 2004 September 24, Compact disc (Box 35, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0241)
  - Jazz Loft Exhibition Audio, undated; 68
    - Jazz Loft Exhibition Audio, undated, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0107)
  - Jazz Loft Exhibition Audio Tracks for Kiosks, undated; 69
    - Exhibition Audio; Jazz Loft Project tracks for listening station kiosks, undated, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0108)
  - Jazz Loft Monk at Town Hall Rough Episode, 2009 March 26; 70
    - Jazz Loft Monk at Town Hall Rough Episode; 3/26/09; 17:46, 2009 March 26, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0115)
  - Jazz Loft Monk Audio Sampler, 2008 November 12; 71
    - Jazz Loft Project Monk Audio Sampler, 2008 November 12, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0104)
  - Jazz Loft Music Sampler, 2004 September; 72
    - W. Eugene Smith Jazz Loft Sampler Music 9/04, 2004 September, Compact disc (Box 32, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0102)
  - Jazz Loft Project Ambient Compilation, 2009 February; 73
    - Jazz Loft Project Ambient Compilation 2/2009 (NYPL), 2009 February, Compact disc (Box 34, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0183)
  - Jazz Loft Project Exhibit NYC, 2010 February 16; 74
    - JLP Exhibit NYC 2/16/10, 2010 February 16, DVD (Box 34, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0011)
  - Jazz Loft Project Exhibition Installation Video, undated; 75
    - Jazz Loft Project Exhibition Installation Video; copyright C. Reid-Eaton, undated, DVD (Box 32, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0008)
  - Jazz Loft Project Oral Histories Excerpts, undated; 76
    - Jazz Loft Project Oral Histories Excerpts, undated, DVD (Box 31, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0004)
  - Jazz Loft Project Oral Histories Excerpts for Web, undated; 77
    - JLP 9.08 Oral History Excerpts; Sam's Bose proposal; DXY 71 doc excerpts, undated, DVD (Box 31, Video-disc RL10001-DVD-0005)
  - Jazz Loft Project Radio Series Sampler, 2009; 78
    - Sampler Jazz Loft Project Radio Series Promotional Copy. Not for broadcast. Not for sale., 2009, Compact disc (Box 31, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0076)
  - Jazz Loft Project Radio Series Sampler, 2009; 79